

Thang Cao Viet

Fullstack Developer

Highly skilled Fullstack Developer with +5 years of experience in designing, developing, and maintaining web applications. Proficient in both front-end and back-end technologies, with a strong understanding of the entire web development process. Always willing to Learn new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

9thWonder VietNam, Nha Trang city, Viet Nam

06/2018 - 06/2023

A website development company in Nha Trang with 50+ employees, formerly a major Digital Agency in the United States. <u>Watch me at 9thWonder VietNam</u>

Fullstack Node.js Developer

06/2018 - 12/2021

- <u>Mazi</u> (06/2018 12/2021)
 - A contract, campaign, job, asset, and research management system.
 - Developed reuseable components and created APIs for frontend use.
 - Wrote tests such as E2E, unit tests, and component tests.
 - Participated in discussions and offered solutions to solve problems.
 - Used technologies: Node.js, Vue.js, Hapi.js, pdftk, MongoDB with Mongoose, Redis, Jest, Cypress, Cucumber.js and AWS (EC2, S3).

Web Developer

01/2022 - 06/2023

- Encompass (01/2022)
 - Design fields, build components, and query data for components.
 - Used technologies: React.js, Gatsby.js, GraphQL and Contentful as the database.
- XOS (05/2022 06/2022)
 - Simulated the entire UI of an XOS machine (an X camera).
 - Worked alone as the only programmer for the project.
 - Used technologies: Vue.js 3 and Tailwind CSS.
- ExakTime, Gravina Windows, Syndeo Institute, Hearsay
 - From 07/2022 04/2023
 - Build modules, create custom widgets, write code tests such as E2E and unit tests. Create plugins and tools to help testers work faster.
 - Used technologies: PHP, Drupal, WordPress, Elementor, Vue.js,
 Cypress, Cucumber.js, jQuery, Tailwind CSS, PHPUnit and MySQL.
- VIOC Oil Change (04/2023): joined and optimized APIs after migration, updated quering for a table (MySQL) with approximately 20 million records.

FREELANCER PROJECTS

- **Shopee CRM**, <u>Shopee Analytics</u>, CRM for Shopee sellers 08/2021 04/2022 Tech: Node.js, Vue.js, Nest.js, MongoDB, Shopee API, AWS.
- **Nike Chat,** Chat system for a team named "Nike" 11/2021 03/2022 Tech: Vue.js, Firebase (Firestore, FCM, Storage)
- **Hotato Extension**, 5k+ users, supports Shopee sellers 04/2022 06/2022 Tech: Node.js, Vue.js, Nest.js, MongoDB, AWS.
- **DAO Chat,** chat system for DAO Entertainment company 03/2022 08/2022 Tech: Node.js, React.js, Firebase, Nest.js, Google drive API, AWS.
- **Coffee Shop Management,** manage a small coffee shop 05/2023 06/2023 Tech: Vue.js, Firebase (Firestore, Hosting).

CONTACT

- · Nha Trang city, Viet Nam
- · +84 368 844 581
- cvthang56th2@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/thang-cao96
- cvthang56th2.github.io

SKILLS

Hard Skills:

- Website development (both Front-end and Back-end)
- Software Testing
 (Unit test and E2E Testing)
- · Architecture Design
- · Agile: SCRUM

Technologies:

- Vue.js
- React.js
- Gatsby.js
- GraphQL
- Hapi.js
- Nest.js
- PHP (Wordpress, Drupal)
- · Cypress and Cucumber.js
- · MongoDB, Mongoose
- Firebase
- · Ruby on Rails (basic)
- · Cloud (AWS, Hostinger basic)

Languages:

- Vietnamese (Native)
- · English (Conversational)

EDUCATION

Nha Trang University

Major: Information Technology

- University Degree (09/2014 – 09/2018)
- Master's Degree,

Graduation thesis: Certificate Management based on Blockchain (06/2020 - present)

Nha Trang city, Viet Nam

OTHER

- · Certified Vue Developer (by VueAcademy 2023)
- Employee of the month (9thWonder VietNam, 04/2023)
- Second prize of the Student Informatics Olympiad (Nha Trang University, 2018)
- Joined the ACM-ICPC team, and our team solved 3/11 problems. (Ho Chi Minh City, 2018)